This tiny dot is a robot. Here it is on
a penny. But the way that it moves is
crazy. It can wiggle all on its own
because they fit a computer on there.
And what happens is you send light to
this part, telling the robot to create
an electric field, which then moves
charged particles in the water, and
therefore the water molecules itself. So
it's not really moving itself, it's
moving the water around it. It's got
built-in temperature sensors, so it can
monitor individual cells in your body.
And the way they report their
temperature measurements is by wiggling
in a kind of Morse code. Are you kidding
me? That's so cute. They cost less than
a penny to make, and they've got some
other ideas for how to use them inside
your body. So to see what, subscribe.